is that something standard you do
pregnant alone and dhaa oh it's
something standard that I do for sure
right so just to just to run through the
hormonal Cascade for for anyone and so
we start biochemically with cholesterol
and you have to have enough cholesterol
to make your hormones and and most
people do sometimes sometimes people are
a little over stened but generally you
have to have actually a cholesterol of
140 to make your hormone so from
cholesterol we make something called
pregnanolone pregnanolone is the mother
hormone it's the precursor to all of the
other hormones and it's also good for
your brain for your memory and your
concentration from pregnant alone we
make progesterone Keeps Us calm helps us
sleep regulates our periods and from
pregnanolone we also make DHEA which is
made in the adrenal glands and has a lot
to do with the resilience to stress and
our overall sense of well-being and then
from the DHEA we make three different
forms of estrogen E1 E2 E3 and then we
also from the DHEA make testosterone so
so yeah like when you when you look at
all the hormones I mean you want
everything to be balanced and and you
have to think we produce a ton of
everything until we're about 25 and then
things start to decline so when I see
just let's say an average patient in her
early 50s or something I mean the
pregnant alone and the DHEA will be low
and so I put them in um to that morning
tablet with the testosterone and I I
think it's important to have all of the
hormones balanced properly now with when
I use injectable testosterone I will
give pregalin and
DHEA SE those are they're just over the
counter supplements actually so I'll
just give them along with the with the
testosterone yeah what are some average
doses for women because I have no ID I
know for men but for women I have no ID
so for women so I usually will Max it
out at 100 and so I'll give like I
usually give it you what in increments
of 25 give or take so
25575 100 just depending on what the
level is and then DHEA will be somewhere
like somewhere up to 10 I usually kind
of Max it out at 10 and these are not
absolute things but I have never really
felt the need to give more than that and
so with the DHEA it's get 2.55 7.5 and
10 and again I just I put them in I put
them in those tablets so a Max dose
would be like 100 pregnant Alone 10 DHEA
and then and then you know however much
testosterone like usually five
testosterone is where I where I feel is
kind of a safe cut off and I'm not
against giving more that but you may
grow facial hair and your clitoris May
enlarge so at your own
[Music]
risk